It feels like summer.
Ah!
Hey, guys!
Wait, what was that?
What was that? Hey!
What's this? What is this? What is this?
Today.
Hey.
Was that Doral today?
No, no, no.
Yay!
You did, too.
No, no, no.
Common sense test!
Oh, a test?
I didn't get it.
Come on in.
Let's go in.
Not at all. My stomach hurts.
And so, ladies and gentlemen...
Jowski's problem test.
I'm so excited!
Like this...
I'm sure!
So, Jowski.
I found some of them a little annoying
Eighth grade.
Well... well... I haven't been here before.
The best. - I forgot.
I forgot. - Education's a bitch.
I mean, I've got an elementary education.
How are your grades?
How good were you in school?  - Top of the class.
You're lying for sure!
Once... once... in middle school or something.
You know, in junior high school? What was your rank?
In my grade.
I think I was in the double digits.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Okay, then.
How far below average were you?
There's a ditch... the 75th percentile.
75th percentile. - That's what you mean?
Over 100 people. - Over 75.
Oh, yes. - It's hard to tell.
I don't understand. - I've never heard that before.
It's a percentage. - It's confusing.
I don't know. - I don't know.
I don't know. - Get ready.
I didn't even know it existed.
But in junior high, I was already a video game freak.
That's why I was so good at video games.
I mean, if it was a game.
I was number two in the world in music.
Not now?
You're fighting in the wrong place.
Where are you?  - I'm a real piece of work.
50 times.
No more lip service. No more of this pretense.
There's no more pretense.
I don't know where I went to school.
I went to cram school.
You went to cram school? That's right, you did.
Stop acting like you don't know me.
Once every 3 months...
There's an exam every three months.
Oh, no, I don't think so.
I'm always the worst at it
You're not allowed to go to cram school.
There were a lot of teams.
They didn't get mad at you? - No, they didn't.
No, they didn't get mad at me.
They were pretty strict. - They weren't that strict.
By the way, I was...
By the way, I was on this one.
There were about 280 of us.
I came in second last.
Wow, that's amazing.
Worst? You think that was funny? It wasn't the worst.
That's pretty good. - Top 15 in the tournament.
That's great.
That's great. Kii, this is so cool.
There's no one who can do it.
I don't know how to do it.
No. I thought I could do it.
So tell me.
I slept all day at school, so it's just looks.
It's just a look.
Oh, man.
Yeah, he's right.
When's it gonna be about looks?
When is it just looks?
No, but this is really what I'm asking for.
Negative promotion
Don't look at it yet.
I'm going to go get ready to drink.
The shrine...
I really don't like it!
Like two hundred kinds of bow...
Two hundred kinds of bow...
I see...
Peco-peco-panpan?
Peco-peco-panpan...
I'm sure...
What I learned
Word subjects.
Wow!
Oh no.
And I got a perfect score of 100
There are 50.
There's 50?
That's a lot.
Japanese.
Arithmetic.
I think there's one more.
What?
Japanese.
Arithmetic, Science, Social Studies, Health Sciences.
Why did you say public health college?
English.
English. English.
Oh, English.
Not my math.
Math.
That's elementary school.
Oh, okay.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, no, no, no.
Scary, scary, scary.
Finally, I didn't go.
Here we go.
What do you think?
Pretty sure this place is dangerous.
No, no, no, no, no.
Dangerous.
This looks bad.
Maybe we'll find it.
Maybe.
Maybe he's hiding.
Okay, everyone, time limit.
15 minutes.
Too short.
Less than 30 points.
That's what we call a red mark.
Less than 30 points?
Red points.
It's a water resources walking quota.
Wow.
Righteousness.
That's not good.
If the derivatives are good...
No one's getting anything out of this.
I'm not here.
I'm not in trouble.
No, you're not.
That's why I'm going with the water group.
And the roasted bus...
With Takuchan.
Even though I'm not here...
Spring will live
Spring is alive
He's smart
That's why
Yuden's in charge.
The problem is that Yuden's not here today.
Yeah.
Well, good luck, everyone.
Okay.
Okay, everyone.
All right.
Let's do it.
Seven times is good.
Seven is good.
Wait.
Oh, my God, this is really, really, really bad.
I'm forgetting something like this.
But why did you write the answer to Q5?
That's the answer.
It's the answer.
Who is this?
You can tell he's a skateboarder.
What? What is it?
Where did you say that?
This is the last problem in the math section.
I've never been skateboarding.
You're sleeping.
Five seconds!
Three, two,
Aaahhh!
Oh, no!
There's not enough time.
It's over!
I'm gonna lose points.
Ah! Ryuuji! Put it down.
No, no, no, no, no.
No way!
These students kept saying
They kept saying that the show wasn't over yet.
Do I have it?
I don't see your name on it.
Yes! Yes!
Okay, you're up.
Okay?
On behalf of the board, please.
Oh! I wrote my name!
Look!
I won!
I'll represent you by name.
They're similar by name.
Here, write Ryogachchi's name on it.
Ryogachchi.
What's Ryogachichi?
If you write Ryogachchi, it might turn into news.
Oh, good, look
Oh, good.
Okay.
What does that mean?
I'll write "Shuya loves you.
Hey, hey, hey.
I love you.
I just love you.
By the way, what was your score, Shuya?
Me?
But you said...
I got 62.
But you said more than half.
You said the second half correctly.
You're missing a lot more than you think.
62.
Oh, shit.
I used to say "until recently.
When I say "until recently"...
I'm talking about, like, Garamene.
Well, I don't know.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
That was surprisingly close.
Shall we go?
Let's start with you, Aloha.
Oh!
First of all...
That's a little much, isn't it?
It's a formula for finding the area of a trapezoid.
Everyone made a lot of mistakes on this one.
Top-bottom
It's a trapezoid.
That's right.
the bottom of a trapezoid
Which is the upper bottom?
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
It's Japanese.
Who said "top and bottom"?
Well, then...
Are you watching?
This was pretty hard.
It's a top-bottom line.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
What country is this?
England.
Oh, you're in England?
Hey!
What's wrong with Chile?
It's South America.
That's a weird reaction.
No way.
Well, at least it's not a coincidence.
I wrote "Chile.
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
That's great!
It's tiny.
Ha-ha-ha-ha
A-ha-ha-ha
I think that's what it means.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
I'm not gonna touch that one.
That's a little out of line.
That's a little out of line, isn't it?
You like Masaoka.
Koge-san.
Kotoge-san.
You do that.
I'm doing the "you look just like him" thing.
That's Kotoge-san's stuff, isn't it?
In Picco Pics.
Yes.
You're a bit of a yan-chan, aren't you?
Yes, that's right.
It was funny before.
Naoyoshi Tokugawa...
Oh, this.
A law equivalent to the "mercy for all living things" law that was issued by the government.
Don't put food on the table afterwards.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
It's still true today.
What law?
Yes, sir.
You can't kill something that has life in it.
You can't kill it.
It's the same thing.
If it was a living thing, I'd have triangulated it.
Oh, wow.
Last thing.
Before you say, "I'm gonna have to put my hands on you.
Say it.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
I feel like I'm supposed to draw a picture
No, that's what they said.
What?
Next is the National Treasure.
I didn't get the National Treasure at all.
There were a few who couldn't do this.
Who can't do this?
Question 8.
Write down how to read.
Yes.
after all
Ha-ha-ha
I've been told this a lot.
This one.
I don't have a license.
It's written on the parking sign.
Of course it is.
Oh, so that's how it is.
I had a license.
So that's how it is.
It's a tree lot.
It's called a tree-lined parking lot.
Right.
It's a parking spot.
That's right.
What the hell is that?
I don't...
Do you have a driver's license?
Eh, arawakun.
Thirty-six points.
Oh!
eh
that's great!
That's great!
What if this thing comes in second place or something?
What would you do?
Not at all!
That's the scariest thing I've ever seen.
It's possible.
That's not good.
Next, Masahito!
Here it comes!
Oh, no!
Oh no!
Masahito-kun...
You got the area of the trapezoid wrong.
Trapezoid
You can draw it so well!
No, I'm sure I'll go crazy
By the way
Area of top and bottom
Where is the upper side, the lower side, and the bottom side?
Myself and life
It's all mixed up.
So it's really very confusing.
I see.
Yes, it's all right.
It's okay. It's okay.
Next.
The capital of the United States.
New York.
Washington.
Yes, sir.
Correct.
Wow, I drew more L.A. than I thought I would.
I drew L.A., too.
I knew I was going to draw America and LA.
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Q9.
What is his name?
A lot.
Gandhi
I miss him.
Because it's not Gandhi.
Who's Gandhi?
I don't know who Gandhi is.
Gandhi.
It's a little difficult to draw a masterpiece three times.
It's hard!
I couldn't do it either.
What's my answer?
student
Heisei era
Tax system
I didn't know
Tax systemTax systemTax system
I wrote something.
I wrote it in my notebook.
I didn't know what it was.
I don't even know what to ask
I don't know what you're talking about.
I don't know what it is.
Wait, wait, wait!
English
ABC
No way!
That's the one you just taught me.
ABCDEFGHIJKLLM
Wow. MUL.
Ew.
That means MUL.
Oh, no, no, no.
It says MUL. It says MUL.
MUL
VWU
Ha-ha-ha-ha
I can say
VWU
I don't want it
Oh no
I don't know why I came in here.
I don't know either.
Thursday
Oh, no!
I knew it!
There's a lot going on at Beth's.
Just today.
Fesday.
It's festival day.
We've been to most of the festivals.
Good's science class
Goode's
Gate
Gwen
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Ha-ha-ha-ha
Gwen
Gwen.
This is so much fun.
But the one that seems to be the most superlative
Gwen.
It's like something or other.
Erika
Masa no Midori Mushi
What is this?
It's watery, but...
It didn't look like that.
ear shell shrimp
It's like vermicelli
This creature
Mitochondrian
Ha-ha-ha-ha
Wow!
Daphnia magna.
Oh, no.
It's Daphnia. Daphnia.
Daphnia.
If Daphnia continues, we can do it.
I can do it.
I got impatient.
That's right.
You're still in a hurry.
You wrote "eventually" at the end.
In the end...
I didn't understand.
I don't know.
So, Masahiro
44 points
Oh!
That's cold.
Cold.
Agata-san
That one went up.
Oh, no!
Look out!
I don't think that's it.
We've been over the hump!
Next up.
Takashi.
Yes, sir.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Takashi.
But I'm not sure.
It's just like you, Takashi.
In one side of this square...
5 centimeters in area.
How do you calculate that?
Random.
Piece by piece
Guess, guess, guess.
Another guess, another guess, another guess.
I see.
I don't understand.
Well, it's one side times one side.
Vertical multiplied by horizontal.
Vertical, horizontal.
So this is where you hang the vertical and the horizontal.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
A-ha-ha-ha
a-ha-ha-ha-ha
Ha-ha-ha-ha
By the way, this angle
I don't know how you calculated this.
Angle a little bit.
Like this.
It came out like this.
eye protractor
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Protractor
I used to do this in elementary school.
American Apostle
Hitney
Ha-ha-ha-ha
Is this Australian?
Already!
I'm not sure about the live
I'm already questioning the live show.
For live
The three great revolutions of the Meiji Restoration have arrived
Oh, this one...
This was probably the most difficult one.
Oh, you're filling it in.
Clothes introduction
Oh
Milk
Introduction of beef pots
Introduction of home appliances
A little likely
Seems possible
Beef casserole is the only thing that doesn't make sense.
During the Meiji Restoration
During the Meiji Era.
Let's say...
Western food was introduced.
At that time, beef hot pot became popular.
Beef casserole was invaded
Beef casserole was invaded.
Why is that the case?
It's true, it's true.
By the way, what do you mean by the introduction of western clothes?
Japanese clothes were the norm in those days.
But by this time...
Soups and shirts
And things like that.
Is that true?
I think it's true.
How do you know that?
How do you have a grocery store?
It's as if it's good. It's as if...
English Question 2.
It's in the past progressive tense.
It means "I was doing at that time...
Taguchi, this is...
It's a desire.
I wanted to sing.
You always say you want to sing.
I want to sing.
I guess it just comes out.
It can't be helped.
It says "that day, that time.
I don't think so.
Even in that place...
I've got "Modakuzumasaka" in my head...
Next, write a comparison with Gugu.
Gggh!
G'day
Guddo was in my head.
Guddy was out.
Good day!
Write the following in English.
What's this?
It looks like Sushi Sauce.
Sushi on the left.
Sushi.
And there's a sauce called Sushi Sauce.
And then on the right...
Sushi Sauce
Sushi Sauce, Sushi Sauce, Sushi Sauce.
Sushi and Sushi Sauce mixed together, Sushi Sauce.
LOL.
Science.
Complete and incomplete metamorphosis
Incomplete metamorphosis
No way.
Pervert enough to get arrested, real pervert.
Wow.
Oh, you're over here.
You're both perverts who could get arrested.
That's bullshit.
You're doing it.
I get a lot of funny answers about that.
You're kidding.
You're supposed to write down the reading of the unit.
It's cubic centimeters.
Ethanol.
It's a liquid.
Oh, it's a liquid.
Liquid.
Sid and Hit, that's why he's already saying it in goriro.
Haneda-Mishima-kan's famous phrase.
The answer is...
Blue mountains and blue mountains
Blue mountains.
Takahashi's answer
Whether you divide and divide, keep your distance
I see.
What do you think of this?
Well...
What do you mean?
It's okay to intervene in various ways.
But sometimes it's important to keep a distance between people.
Takahashi, I'm scared.
Mishimakan Haneda said that, right?
I see.
And that's the meaning of the old sentence.
I want to brush my shoulders.
It means "disgraceful.
Oh, it's disgraceful.
I was really pissed off because I couldn't do it, wasn't I?
I see.
That's how I was feeling at the time.
It's all coming out now, isn't it?
What do you mean, you want to pay him off?
Takahashi, in the end...
After all...
Aloha was a mistake after all.
That's true.
Here's what I learned.
Month by month, month by month...
All right, that's enough.
No, it's like an octopus.
It's like a rope.
It's like an octopus.
A bug.
Bugs.
That didn't come up at all.
Insects.
Takahashi, 48 points.
Oh!
Surprisingly...
Hey, hey, hey... bottom of the list.
This one...
Next.
Shall we move on?
Ah!
But the order might be irrelevant.
I don't know.
You're right.
It had something to do with it.
1 meter.
0.1 cm.
Oh, my God.
Oh, no.
It felt like 1mm.
I made a mistake.
I read "1mm".
It felt like 1mm.
I see.
No, it depends on how you look at it.
But I see it now.
Now I see it says "1 meter".
No, no, no.
I'm thinking it right.
Of course it's 100 cm.
Why do you think that?
I wrote 0 in the real test.
It's zero!
The formula for finding the area of a trapezoid.
I don't know.
I don't know it.
You don't know it.
I don't know anything about that.
I don't know it.
I don't know.
You don't use it in society, trapezoid
Desirable sex
Angle.
How do you know the angle?
I don't know.
I'm new to all of this so far.
Well, I'm new at this.
How do you know?
I'll write it at 80 degrees.
I write at 80 degrees and the total is...
That's right.
I see.
I see... a triangular watch.
You're Baron.
I'm a little...
You're the one who writes square watches.
What the hell?
You're right.
Ex is the bottom line.
Ex is the bottom line
Society, society, society
Society
Society is in trouble
Oh, no!
Stop it! Stop it!
You only gave me one question!
Social Studies.
Social Studies...
Q2.
I thought you wrote four.
Yes, yes, yes.
Ten-hime
I'm doing all of them like that.
That's right.
Kagawa
Okay, Kagawa.
Tokushima
Oh!
I got it right.
One more.
One more, but it doesn't come up every time.
I'm trying to write it in threes.
One more, but it doesn't come up.
Every time
Koihachi
Founded in 1948
Headquartered in Geneva, Switzerland
WHO and
what role it plays
yes
World Hot Open
It's kind of warm
That's what I'm talking about.
It's warm.
No, it's not.
What does that mean?
That's Geneva.
What?
Well, I mean, it's really...
Open your warm hearts.
I just looked at it, and it says 1 meter.
Let's go out in the world and hold hands like this.
We'll...
Let's be friends
Hey.
I'm not very good at...
I'm not good at...
I mean it.
Bleep.
Is he your friend?
Shiki-kun
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
That's right.
It says "what's your name".
It doesn't say "full name".
It says "name".
It doesn't.
Why?
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Oh, my God.
A to Z.
Yes, sir.
Can I ask you to read it out loud?
Sure, that part's fast.
A B C D E F G H I J K N
Oh.
There.
Slow down.
A B C D E F G
H I J K L M M
Ah.
Oh, that's the one that got moved.
L M M
Wow.
That's good.
Or the other way around.
This is no good.
You're really limiting it a bit.
from here
That's enough!
What is it?
December, answer in English.
English?
I refuse.
LOL!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm pissed off.
I'm pissed off because you peeked in my writing.
I was ordered to...
Write in English on Thursday.
Yeah.
I mean, it's not Monday.
Yeah, that's for sure.
LOL.
That's not fair.
I'd like to be excused.
Excuse me?
It's not funny when I have bad eyesight.
What is it?
One centimeter.
Yes, yes, yes.
Square centimeters on the other hand.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
What is this?
It says centimeters on the one hand.
LOL.
This one.
It says "one centimeter".
What? It's different.
It's definitely not the same.
I'll do this one.
Yes, yes, yes.
Bang!
I don't know, maybe I shouldn't fake it so good.
Don't do that.
Don't what?
LOL!
It's a circle.
It's a circle!
All right.
This one too.
What's this?
Make a word of the crane and make a sentence.
Seriously, if it wasn't for the crane word, we'd be in serious trouble.
Watch out!
LOL!
You're kidding me.
That's...
That's it.
It's like a bug alert, isn't it?
No, it's not.
I really don't know.
It's like, "Thank God I have this.
Yes, it did.
Someone in authority, like a leader...
Knowledgeable decision makers.
Yeah.
So...
That's great.
So you've had that kind of experience then.
Not yet.
Why am I in the triangle?
LOL!
I owe my life to the cranes.
Almost the same.
But I thought it was the end of my life.
LOL!
Not to the end.
Not that far.
Yabba.
Yes, sir.
Forty-four points.
That's great.
That's just like me.
I'm gonna finish.
What's your score?
Thirty-six.
Oh!
LOL.
Wow!
Rust.
I'd like to go
Gah!
I don't know... yet.
You're doing great in math.
Surprisingly...
I got it! I got it!
By the way, this angle...
What's the math?
One third.
One-third.
By the way, how many degrees do you think this is?
How many degrees is this?
One-third.
High tenths.
It's like this.
Oh!
Right here.
This is it.
This is...
Society
Kouichi Honshu
It's a piece of shit.
This... is a trick.
I almost fell for it, too.
Hokkaido.
This is Aomori.
What's "Hokkaido"?
Hokkaido.
What is the third magnitude star of Aomori?
Aomori.
Yes, I'm sorry.
Q7: An example of compassion on a long road.
Yes, I'm sorry
What kind of law is it?
It's important
Rice.
What?
What do you do with it?
What are you going to do with the rice?
I'm going to make them make rice.
I want to make him happy.
That's it!
Brain-Den Brain-Den
Some kind of Brain-Den or Danden
Tanden
Tanden is
I want to do Honden Eden
ah yes, that's right
ah ah ah
I thought so
How I want to Eden the main shrine
How I want to Eden the main hall
How I want to Eden the main building
This person's name is really difficult, isn't it?
No way!
Ryunosuke Akutagawa
He's wearing a close-cropped head.
Even if you cut it all off...
I'd rather have this hair...
You...
You have the most hair.
Of all the imposters, you have the most Montiles.
You.
You're not good at this, Yuki
You were so close.
Eh, that's pretty low.
Question 2.
Who's talking?
Good's hook.
No, it's not...
It's really hard!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no...
Can I ask you to read it?
Good's...
In the eye.
Bat.
What does this mean?
It says "BAT.
Bat.
This one.
It's not standing up.
What is all of it?
science
Green Beetle
Are you kidding me?
No, it's a greenfly.
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
That's...
By the way.
Just in case.
In Yuki's mind.
If this is a Green Beetle...
Next question
This creature's name is Green Beetle.
It's written on it.
No, no.
Like a roller creation.
No, no, no.
This one.
Write the same thing.
Okay, let's do this.
I'm writing.
Look at this.
Oh, lettuce.
Lettuce beans.
Letta beans.
Say something like...
Oh, you too
Are you kidding me?
yes
to the question
Who's that without a third-grade dream?
I don't know what's going on
I don't understand
It's good
Isn't it?
It's good!
What's this?
Next.
Change the verbs to honorifics.
Yes. - Yes.
Say, see, eat, wear.
Eat. Wear.
Well, that's the answer.
I don't know the answer.
I don't know.
I don't know the answer to your question.
You will see
see
eat
Uh...
It's hard to say "to be called".
I say it as such a word
Three times like that
Well, let me tell you...
Eat.
eat
OK
OKI
what kind of
offshore
Breathing
That's what it means, isn't it?
That's what it means.
That's why you're here.
Eat.
Why is everything from the top?
O-e-e-e.
I thought you were being polite.
It's not polite.
That's one way to look at it.
What's with that guy?
Ha-ha-ha.
I knew it.
The month is short.
At last.
It was difficult
Keikyuu
I mean "Keikyuu".
Even if it's a month off.
ehehe
My handwriting is so dirty!
When I say "moon vacation", it's totally wrong.
So, 34 points for Yuki!
Eh?
Ehh...
Thirty-six.
1 minute
Uh-uh.
I can take the last three minutes of this ride home.
I can ride this last three minutes home.
You know what?
So...
First place, Takase Yanen
That's good!
Well, well, well...
I'm scared of acorns
2nd place, Masahiro Ryomachi
Awesome!
3rd place - Aloha!
Yay!
Amazing!
4th place, Yuki!
Thanks for your hard work!
I love it!
You didn't make it in time.
Don't film my music video!
I didn't write it.
How was it?
Did you miss it?
Did you miss it or want to do it a little more?
There was no "I want to do it some more.
I don't want to do it again.
Next time, if you're on the verge of a red mark...
Yuki and I...
I'm good, right?
No, we'll have a battle of the stupidest students in the class of "koyomi".
I'd like to include Takuya Kusakawa in it.
I see.
Forget it... it's man vs. man show.
Two points is still an error.
Wow, I didn't think it'd be a win.
Oh, it's over
It's over.